export const chapter = "Chapter -16: Prepositions";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question: "Where is a Preposition generally placed in a sentence?",
          optionA: "After its object",
          optionB: "Before its object",
          optionC: "Both A and B",
          correctAnswer: "Before its object",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In which case can a Preposition be placed after its object?",
          optionA: "When a proper noun is used",
          optionB: "When a conjunction is used",
          optionC: "When an interrogative pronoun is used",
          correctAnswer: "When an interrogative pronoun is used",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Identify the correct preposition in the sentence: 'She took a magazine __ the cupboard.'",
          optionA: "on",
          optionB: "from",
          optionC: "into",
          correctAnswer: "from",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the preposition in the sentence: 'The students reached school __ time.'",
          optionA: "at",
          optionB: "in",
          optionC: "on",
          correctAnswer: "in",
        },
        {
          question: "Which preposition is used to indicate a location?",
          optionA: "on",
          optionB: "in",
          optionC: "with",
          correctAnswer: "in",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Choose the correct preposition in the sentence: 'She wrote a letter __ a blue pen.'",
          optionA: "at",
          optionB: "with",
          optionC: "in",
          correctAnswer: "with",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'The pencil is __ the book,' what is the correct preposition?",
          optionA: "on",
          optionB: "in",
          optionC: "at",
          correctAnswer: "on",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which preposition is used to express the idea of time in 'The birthday party will be held __ next Sunday.'?",
          optionA: "on",
          optionB: "at",
          optionC: "in",
          correctAnswer: "on",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Identify the preposition in the sentence: 'There is friendship __ Seema and Aruna.'",
          optionA: "between",
          optionB: "with",
          optionC: "in",
          correctAnswer: "between",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the correct preposition in the sentence: 'He hit the dog __ a stick.'?",
          optionA: "on",
          optionB: "with",
          optionC: "at",
          correctAnswer: "with",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "In a sentence, a Preposition is generally placed ____________ its Object:",
          optionA: "after",
          optionB: "before",
          optionC: "with",
          correctAnswer: "before",
        },
        {
          question:
            "A Preposition can be placed after its Object when ____________ Pronoun is used in a sentence:",
          optionA: "demonstrative",
          optionB: "interrogative",
          optionC: "relative",
          correctAnswer: "interrogative",
        },
        {
          question: "Read some common Prepositions: after, among, ____________",
          optionA: "against",
          optionB: "about",
          optionC: "along",
          correctAnswer: "about",
        },
        {
          question: "What is he thinking ____________?",
          optionA: "off",
          optionB: "on",
          optionC: "of",
          correctAnswer: "of",
        },
        {
          question: "She goes to office ____________ foot.",
          optionA: "by",
          optionB: "on",
          optionC: "with",
          correctAnswer: "on",
        },
        {
          question: "The birthday party will be held ____________ next Sunday.",
          optionA: "at",
          optionB: "on",
          optionC: "in",
          correctAnswer: "on",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The teacher divided the chocolate ____________ two friends.",
          optionA: "between",
          optionB: "among",
          optionC: "within",
          correctAnswer: "between",
        },
        {
          question:
            "There is no friendly relation ____________ India and Pakistan.",
          optionA: "among",
          optionB: "between",
          optionC: "with",
          correctAnswer: "between",
        },
        {
          question: "The students reached school ____________ time.",
          optionA: "in",
          optionB: "on",
          optionC: "at",
          correctAnswer: "in",
        },
        {
          question: "The pencil is ____________ the book.",
          optionA: "over",
          optionB: "on",
          optionC: "under",
          correctAnswer: "on",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "An adverb is a type of word that adds to the meaning of a noun or pronoun in a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Prepositions are always placed after their object in a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Interrogative pronouns can cause prepositions to be placed after their objects.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of manner demonstrate how often an action takes place.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs of time indicate when an action takes place.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Many adverbs of manner are formed by adding -ing to adjectives.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of frequency or number show where an action takes place.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question: "Adverbs can only modify verbs in a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adverbs of frequency show how often an action takes place.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Prepositions are used to express the idea of time in a sentence.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
